<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <record id="paperformat_model_agreement" model="report.paperformat">
        <field name="name">Self Certificate PaperFormat</field>
        <field name="default" eval="True"/>
        <field name="format">A4</field>
        <field name="orientation">Portrait</field>
        <field name="margin_top">18</field>
        <field name="margin_left">8</field>
        <field name="margin_right">8</field>
        <field name="dpi">90</field>
    </record>

    <record id="model_agreement" model="ir.actions.report">
        <field name="name">Model Agreement</field>
        <field name="model">project.task</field>
        <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
        <field name="report_name">arclight_solar_report.report_model_agreement</field>
        <field name="report_file">arclight_solar_report.report_model_agreement</field>
        <field name="binding_model_id" ref="project.model_project_task"/>
        <field name="binding_type">report</field>
        <field name="paperformat_id" ref="arclight_solar_report.paperformat_model_agreement"/>
    </record>

    <record id="arclight_solar_report.report_model_agreement" model="ir.ui.view">
        <field name="name">arclight_solar_report.report_model_agreement</field>
        <field name="type">qweb</field>
        <field name="arch" type="xml">
            <template id="report_model_agreement" t-name="arclight_solar_report.report_model_agreement">
                <t t-call="web.html_container">
                    <t t-call="web.external_layout">
                        <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                            <div class="page">

                                <h5 style="text-align:center; font-weight:bold; text-decoration: underline;">Model Agreement</h5>
                                <h5 style="text-align:center; font-weight:bold; text-decoration: underline;">Between</h5>
                                <h5 style="text-align:center; font-weight:bold;">Applicant and the registered/empanelled
                                    Vendor for installation of rooftop solar system in residential house of the
                                    Applicant under simplified procedure of Rooftop Solar Programme Ph- II
                                </h5>

                                <p style="text-align:justify; line-height:1.5; font-size:18px;">
                                    This agreement is executed on -------(Day)------(Month)-------(Year) for design,
                                    installation, undersimplified procedure of Rooftop Solar Programme Ph-II.
                                </p>

                                <p style="text-align:center; line-height:1.5; font-size:18px;">Between</p>

                                <p style="text-align:justify; line-height:1.5; font-size:18px;">
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.consumer_name_mis"/></u></b>
                                    (Name of Applicant) having residential electricity connection with consumer number
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.consumer_no_mis"/></u></b>
                                    from
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.address_street1"/>,<t t-esc="doc.address_street2"/>,
                                        District:<t t-esc="doc.district"/>,
                                        State:<t t-esc="doc.consumer_state_mis"/>
                                    </u></b>
                                    (hereinafter referred as Applicant).
                                </p>

                                <p style="text-align:center; line-height:1.5; font-size:20px; font-weight:bold;">And</p>

                                <p style="text-align:justify; line-height:1.5; font-size:18px;">
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.consumer_name_mis"/></u></b>
                                    (Name of Vendor) is registered/ empanelled with the
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.consumer_name_mis"/></u></b>
                                    hereinafter referred as DISCOM) and is having registered/functional office at
                                    <b><u><t t-esc="doc.consumer_name_mis"/></u></b>
                                    (hereinafter referred as Vendor).Both Applicant and the Vendor are jointly referred as Parties.
                                </p>

                                <p style="text-align:center; line-height:1.5; font-size:20px; font-weight:bold;">Whereas</p>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>     - The Applicant intends to install rooftop solar system under simplified
                                        procedure of Rooftop SolarProgramme Ph-II of the MNRE.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>     - The Vendor is registered/empanelled vendor with DISCOM for installation of
                                        rooftop solar under MNRE Schemes. The Vendor satisfies all the existing
                                        regulation pertaining to electrical safety and license in the respective state
                                        and it is not debarred or blacklisted from undertaking any such installations by
                                        any state/central Government agency.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>     - Both the parties are mutually agreed and understand their roles and
                                        responsibilities and have noliability to any other agency/firm/stakeholder
                                        especially to DISCOM and MNRE.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">1. GENERAL TERMS:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>1.1. The Applicant hereby represents and warrants that the Applicant has the sole
                                        legal capacity to enter into this Agreement and authorise the construction,
                                        installation and commissioning of the Rooftop Solar System (<b>“RTS System”</b>) which
                                        is inclusive of Balance of System (<b>“BoS”</b>) on the Applicant’s premises
                                        (<b>“Applicant Site”</b>). The Vendor reserves its right to verify ownership of the
                                        Applicant Site and Applicant covenants to co-operate and provide all information
                                        and documentation required by the Vendor for the same.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>1.2. Vendor may propose changes to the scope, nature and or schedule of the
                                        services being performed under this Agreement. All proposed changes must be
                                        mutually agreed between the Parties. If Parties fail to agree on the variation
                                        proposed, either Party may terminate this Agreement by serving notice as per
                                        Clause 13.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>1.3. The Applicant understands and agrees that future changes in load,
                                        electricity usage patterns and/or electricity tariffs may affect the economics
                                        of the RTS System and these factors have not been and cannot be considered in
                                        any analysis or quotation provided by Vendor or its Authorized Persons (defined
                                        below).
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">2. RTS System</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>2.1. Total capacity of RTS System will be minimum <b><u>4.56kWp</u></b>.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>2.2. The Solar modules, inverters and BoS will confirm to minimum specifications
                                        and DCR requirement of MNRE.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>2.3. Solar modules of <b><u>ADANI PANEL</u></b> make, model, <b><u>565 WP</u></b>
                                        capacity each and<b><u>20. 83</u></b> efficiency willbe procured and installed
                                        by the Vendor
                                    </p>
                                    <p>2.4. Solar inverter of <b><u>SOLARYAAN</u></b> make, model, <b><u>3.3 kW</u></b>
                                        rated output capacity will be procured and installed by the Vendor
                                    </p>
                                    <p>2.5. Module mounting structure has to withstand minimum wind load pressure as
                                        specified by MNRE.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>2.6. Other BoS installations shall be as per best industry practice with all
                                        safety and protection gears installed by the vendor.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">3. PRICE AND PAYMENT TERMS</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>3.1. The cost of RTS System will be Rs.        (to be decided mutually).
                                        The Applicant shall paythe total cost to the Vendor as under:<br/>
                                        (i) 10% as an advance on confirmation of the order;<br/>
                                        (ii) 80% against Proforma Invoice (PI) before dispatch of solar panels,
                                        inverters and other BoS items to be delivered;<br/>
                                        (iii) 10% after installation and commissioning of the RTS System.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>3.2. The order value and payment terms are fixed and will not be subject to any
                                        adjustment except as approved in writing by Vendor. The payment shall be made
                                        only through bankers’ cheque
                                        / NEFT / RTGS / online payment portal as intimated by Vendor. No cash payments
                                        shall be accepted by Vendor or its Authorised Person.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">4. REPRESENTATIONS MADE BY THE APPLICANT:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>The Applicant acknowledges and agrees that:</p>
                                    <p>4.1. any timeline or schedule shared by Vendor for the provision of services and
                                        delivery of the RTS System is only an estimate and Vendor will not be liable for
                                        any delay that is not attributable to Vendor;
                                    </p>
                                    <p>4.2. all information disclosed by the Applicant to Vendor in connection with the
                                        supply of the RTS System (or any part thereof), services and generation
                                        estimation (including, without limitation, the load profile and power bill) are
                                        true and accurate, and acknowledges that Vendor has relied on the information
                                        produced by the Applicant to Customize the RTS System layout and BoS design for
                                        the purposes of this Agreement;
                                    </p>
                                    <p>4.3. all descriptive specifications, illustrations, drawings, data, dimensions,
                                        quotation, fact sheets, price lists and any advertising material
                                        circulated/published/provided by Vendor are approximate only;
                                    </p>
                                    <p>4.4. any drawings, pre-feasibility report, specifications and plans composed by
                                        Vendor shall require the Applicant’s approval within 5 (five) days of its
                                        receipt by electronic mail to Vendor and if the Applicant does not respond
                                        within this period, the drawings, specifications or plans shall be final and
                                        deemed to have been approved by the Applicant;
                                    </p>
                                    <p>4.5. the Applicant shall not use the RTS System or any part thereof, other than
                                        in accordance with the product manufacturer’s specifications, and covenants that
                                        any risk arising from misuse or/and misappropriate use shall be to the account
                                        of the Applicant alone.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>4.6. The Applicant represents, warrants and covenants that:
                                        <br/>
                                        (i) all electrical and plumbing infrastructure at the Applicant Site are in
                                        conformity with applicable laws;
                                        <br/>
                                        (ii) the Applicant has the legal capacity to permit unfettered access to Vendor
                                        and its Authorized Persons for the purposes of execution and performance of this
                                        Agreement;
                                        <br/>
                                        (iii) the Applicant has and will provide requisite power, water and other
                                        requisite resources and storage facilities for construction, installation,
                                        operation and maintenance of the RTS System;
                                        <br/>
                                        (iv) the Applicant will provide support for site fabrication of structure,
                                        assembly and fitting of module mounting structure at Applicant Site;
                                        <br/>
                                        (v) the Applicant will ensure that the Applicant Site is shadow free and free of
                                        all encumbrances during the lifetime of the RTS System;
                                        <br/>
                                        (vi) licant should ensure that the Applicant regularly cleans and ensures
                                        accessibility and safety to he RTS Systm, as required by Vendor and dusting
                                        frequency in the premises.
                                        <br/>
                                        (vii) Vendor is entitled to permit geo-tagging of the Applicant Site as a Vendor
                                        installation site;
                                        <br/>
                                        (viii) Unless otherwise intimated by the Applicant in writing, Vendor is
                                        entitled to take photographs, videos and testimonials of the Applicant and the
                                        Applicant Site, and to create content which will become the property of Vendor
                                        and the same can be freely used by Vendor as part of its promotional and
                                        marketing activities across all platforms as it deems fit;
                                        <br/>
                                        (ix) the Applicant validates the stability of the Applicant Site for the
                                        installation of the RTS System.
                                        <br/>
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">5. MAINTENANCE:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>5.1. Vendor shall provide five-year free workmanship maintenance. Vendor shall
                                        visit the Applicant’s premises at least once every quarter after commissioning
                                        of the RTS System for maintenance purposes.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>5.2. During such maintenance visit, Vendor shall check all nuts and bolts, fuses,
                                        earth resistance and other consumables in respect of the RTS System to ensure
                                        that it is in good working condition.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>5.3. Cleaning requirement/expectation from the Applicant side – Applicant
                                        responsibility, minimum expectation from Applicant that it will be cleaned
                                        regularly as per the dusting frequency.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">6. ACCESS AND RIGHT OF ENTRY:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>6.1. The Applicant hereby grants permission to Vendor and its authorized
                                        personnel, representatives, associates, officers, employees, financing agents,
                                        subcontractors (<b><u>“Authorized Persons”</u></b>) to enter the Applicant Site for the
                                        purposes of:<br/>
                                        (a) conducting feasibility study;<br/>
                                        (b) storing the RTS System/any part thereof;<br/>
                                        (c) installing the RTS System;<br/>
                                        (d) inspecting the RTS System;<br/>
                                        (e) conducting repairs and maintenance to the RTS System;<br/>
                                        (f) removing the RTS System (or any part thereof), if necessary for any reason
                                        whatsoever;<br/>
                                        (g) Such other matters as necessary to execute and perform its rights and
                                        obligations under this Agreement.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>6.2. The Applicant shall ensure that third-party consents necessary for the
                                        Authorized Persons to access the Applicant Site are obtained prior to
                                        commencement of services under this Agreement.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">7. WARRANTIES:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>7.1. Product Warranty: The Applicant shall be entitled to manufacturers’
                                        warranty. Any warranty in relation to RTS System supplied to the Applicant by
                                        Vendor under this Agreement is limited to the warranty given by the manufacturer
                                        of the RTS System (or any part thereof) to Vendor.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>7.2. Installation Warranty: Vendor warrants that all installations shall be free
                                        from workmanship defects or BOS defects for a period of five years from the date
                                        of installation of the RTS System. The warranty is limited to Vendor rectifying
                                        the workmanship or BOS defects at Vendor’s expense in respect of those defects
                                        reported by the Applicant, in writing. The Applicant is obliged and liable to
                                        report such defects within 15 (fifteen) days of occurrence of such defect.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>7.3. Subject to manufacturer warranty, Vendor warrants that the solar modules
                                        supplied herein shall have tolerance within a five percentage range (+/-5%). The
                                        peak-power point voltage and the peak-power point current of any supplied solar
                                        module and/or any module string (series connected modules) shall not vary by
                                        more than 5% (five percent) from the respective arithmetic means for all modules
                                        and/or for all module strings, as the case may be, provided the RTS System is
                                        properly maintained and the Applicant Site is free from shadow at the time of
                                        operatiVon ofthe RTS Sstem.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>7.4. Exceptions for warranty:
                                        <br/>
                                        (a) Any attempt by any person other than Vendor or its Authorised Persons to
                                        adjust, modify, repair or provide maintenance to the RTS System, shall
                                        disentitle the Applicant of the warranty provided by Vendor hereunder.
                                        <br/>
                                        (b) Vendor shall not be liable for any degeneration or damage to the RTS System
                                        due to any action or inaction on the part of the Applicant.
                                        <br/>
                                        (c) Vendor shall not be bound or liable to remedy any damage, fault, failure or
                                        malfunction of the RTS System owing to external causes, including but not
                                        limited to accidents, misuse, neglect, if usage and/or storage and/or
                                        installation are non-confirming to product instructions, modifications by the
                                        Applicant leading to shading or accessibility issues, failure to perform
                                        required maintenance, normal wear and tear, Force Majeure Event, or negligence
                                        or default attributable to the Applicant.
                                        <br/>
                                        (d) Vendor shall not be liable to repair or remedy any accessories or parts
                                        added to the RTS System that were not originally sourced by Vendor to the
                                        Applicant.
                                        <br/>
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">8. PERFORMANCE GUARANTEE</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>8.1. Vendor guarantees minimum system performance ratio of 75% as per performance
                                        ratio test carried out in adherence to IEC 61724 or equivalent BIS for a period
                                        of five years.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">9. INSURANCE:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>9.1. Vendor may, at its sole discretion, obtain insurance covering risks of
                                        loss/damage to the RTS System (any part thereof) during transit from Vendor’s
                                        warehouse until delivery to the Applicant Site and until installation and
                                        commissioning.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>9.2. Thereafter, all risk shall pass on to the Applicant and the Applicant may
                                        accordingly procure relevant insurances.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">10. CANCELLATION:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>10.1. The Applicant may cancel the order placed on Vendor within 7 (seven) days
                                        from the date of remittance of advance money or the date of order acceptance,
                                        whichever is earlier (<b><u>“Order Confirmation”</u></b>) by serving notice as
                                        per Clause 13.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>10.2. If the Applicant cancels the order after the expiry of 7 (seven) days from
                                        the date of Order Form, the Applicant shall be liable to pay Vendor, a
                                        cancellation fee of XX% of the total order value plus costs and expenses
                                        incurred by Vendor, including, costs for labour, design, return of products,
                                        administrative costs, subvention costs.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>10.3. Notwithstanding the aforesaid, the Applicant shall not be entitled to
                                        cancel the Order Form after Vendor has dispatched the RTS System (or any part
                                        thereof, including BOS) to the Applicant Site. If Applicant chooses to terminate
                                        the Order Form after dispatch, the entire amount paid by the Applicant till
                                        date, shall be forfeited by Vendor.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND INDEMNITY:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>11.1. To the extent that terms implied by law apply to the RTS System and the
                                        services rendered under this Agreement, Vendor’s liability for any breach of
                                        those terms is limited to:<br/>
                                        (a) repairing or replacing the RTS System/any part thereof, as applicable; or<br/>
                                        (b) Refund of the moneys paid by the Applicant to Vendor, if Vendor cannot
                                        fulfil the order.<br/>
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND INDEMNITY:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>11.1. To the extent that terms implied by law apply to the RTS System and the
                                        services rendered under this Agreement, Vendor’s liability for any breach of
                                        those terms is limited to:<br/>
                                        (a) repairing or replacing the RTS System/any part thereof, as applicable; or<br/>
                                        (b) Refund of the moneys paid by the Applicant to Vendor, if Vendor cannot
                                        fulfil the order.<br/>
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">12. SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>12.1. If the Applicant fails to pay any sum due under this Agreement on the due
                                        date, Vendor may, in addition to its other rights under this Agreement, suspend
                                        its obligations under this Agreement until all outstanding amounts (including
                                        interest due) are paid.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">13. NOTICES:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>13.1. Any notice or other communication under this Agreement to Vendor and or to
                                        the Applicant, shall be in writing, in English language and shall be delivered
                                        or sent: (a) by electronic mail and/or (b) by hand delivery or registered
                                        post/courier, at the registered address of Applicant/Vendor.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">14. FORCE MAJEURE EVENT:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>14.1. Neither Party shall be in default due to any delay or failure to perform
                                        its/his/her/their obligations under this Agreement which arises from or is a
                                        consequence of occurrence of an event which is beyond the reasonable control of
                                        such Party, and which makes performance of its/his/her/their obligations under
                                        this Agreement impossible or so impractical as reasonably to be considered
                                        impossible in the circumstances, and includes, but is not limited to, war, riot,
                                        civil disorder, earthquake, fire, explosion, storm, flood or other adverse
                                        weather conditions, pandemic, epidemic, embargo, strikes, lockouts, labour
                                        difficulties, other industrial action, acts of government, unavailability of
                                        equipment from vendor, changes requested by the Applicant (<b><u>“Force Majeure
                                        Event”</u></b>).
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <h4 style="font-weight:bold;">15. GOVERNING LAW AND DISPUTE RESOLUTION:</h4>

                                <div style="text-align:justify; font-size:18px;">
                                    <p>15.1. The interpretation and enforcement of this Agreement shall be governed by
                                        the laws of India
                                    </p>
                                    <p>15.2. In the event of any dispute, controversy or difference between the Parties
                                        arising out of, or relating to this Agreement (“Dispute”), both Parties shall
                                        make an effort to resolve the Dispute in good faith, failing which, any Party to
                                        the Dispute shall be entitled to refer the Dispute to arbitration to resolve the
                                        Dispute in the manner set out in this Clause. The rights and obligations of the
                                        Parties under this Agreement shall remain in full force and effect pending the
                                        award in such arbitration proceeding.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>15.3. The arbitration proceeding shall be governed by the provisions of the
                                        Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996 and shall be settled by a sole arbitrator
                                        mutually appointed by the Parties.
                                    </p>
                                </div>

                                <br/><br/>

                                <div style="display: flex; justify-content: space-between;  font-size:18px;">
                                    <div>(Applicant)<br/><br/>
                                        Witness<br/><br/>
                                        NAITIKBHAI PANCHAL<br/><br/>
                                        ATULBHAI CHAUDHARI
                                    </div>
                                    <div>(Vendor)<br/>
                                        <b><u>MAHISAGAR SOLAR ENERGY</u></b>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </t>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </template>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>